Guide to the Montana State Prison records 1864-1974
Montana Historical Society
- Montana State Prison
  - Prisoner Records
    - Prisoner description sheets: Carl Frodsham, Frank Phylander Frodsham, Jerome Millard (Jerry) Froshaug, Cecil Frost, Donald Frost, Henri Froustey, Darrol Froze, H. Harvey Fry, James R. Fuci (Fucci), Elvin Fuhrman, Robert Patterson Fulks, Al. Fuller (alias Harrison Kennedy), Elmer Fuller, Fred Franklin Fuller, George Fuller, Ralph J. Fuller, Charles N. Fulmer, Jim Fung, Ernest Funk, William Furnish, Joe S. Furst, Lewis James Furstenau, George A. Furthmeyer, Ira Fuson, Walter Fuson, Joe Gabanna, Philip Adolph Gaber, George C. Gable, David Gabrielson, Harry Barton Gadbaw, Edward Charles Gaebe, Leslie L. Gaffney, Robert Frederick Gage, Lloyd C. Gaine, Clyde Gaines, Ellie Gaines, James Ellie Gaines, Max L. Gaines, Jose Gaitan, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 60/6)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Arthur Galahan, Arthur H. Galahan (alias “Buzz” Galahan), Leo J. Galahan, James Gale, James Victor Galenena, Clarence Gallagher, H.N. Gallagher, James Gallagher, James Gallagher, Jerry Gallagher, Vincent Gallagher, William Gallagher, Carl Joe Gallin, John Gallineau, Dave Gallo, Marvin William Galloupe (Cheetum), Peter Gallucci, Robert Gallus, Jack L. Galstad, Charles Galvin, Allen G. Gamble, N.W. Gamble, Leland Clyde Gammon, Larry (Leland) Gamron, Larry Gangier, Henry Ganier, Tony Ganni, Barney Gannon, Chas. A. Gaog., Abraham Garcia, Agistin Garcia, Charles Garcia, Domingo Garcia, Fausto Garcia (Lopez), Frank Garcia, Frank Garcia, Joe Garcia, Joe Garcia, John Richard Garcia, Juan Emanuel Garcia, Jose M. Garcia, Jose V. Garcia, Larry Garcia, Lewis Herman Garcia, Louis Garcia, Rique Garcia, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 60/7)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Roy Garcia, Santos Garcia, Louie Gardepe (alias Louie Gardipee), Kenneth Gardiner, Ray Gardiner, A.P. (Alphonse) Garding, Alfred Gardipee, Benjamin Gardipee, Edward Gardipee, George Gardipee, Henry Gardipee (sometimes known as Little Blaze), (Henry) Richard Gardipee, Robert Alexander Gardipee, Carl Eugene Gardner, Clifford Orley Gardner, Ernest H. Gardner, Fred Gardner, Fred W. Gardner, Jack Gardner, Ray Gardy, James Garland, William Garland, LaVern Lloyd Garmann, Cessam Garner, Emmet Garner, Harold Payne Garner, Mable Garner, Otis Garner, Walter Garner, Walter Garner, Walter Buck Garner, William Garner, Cecil Garner, Charles Garrett, John Earl Garrett, Johnny L. Garrett (alias Johnny Lee), Lyle (Henry) Garrett, Omer Dennis Garrett (alias Earl Kent), Utah Earl Garrett, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 60/8)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Everett Garrick, Will Albert Garrin, Lewis B. Garrison, Roy Garroutte, Edward Garswick, John Garvey, Seward P. Garwood, Arture Gonzales Garza, Antonio (Tony) Hernandez Gascar, H.J. (Henry Joseph) Gaskill, Francis Gatecloux, Arthur L. Gates, Earl Edward Gates, Lewis Alfred Gates, Ben Gathany, Richard Wayne Gatlin, John Gaub, Gloria Gaudry, Victor Gaudry (alias Victor Davis and Vital Gaudry), Jacob Gaught, Henry Gault, H.E. (Henry Edward) Gause Jr., Orville Gauthier, Roger Gauthier, Frank Gavard, Reginald Gay, Joseph Gaydos, Harry Gaylord, Alex Gaynor, Max (Louis or Lewis) Geaudry, Harold Gebhardt, Marvin Gee, Maurice Arnold Geerdes, Leonard Geesey, Louis E. Geis, John S. Gelgut, Charled M. (Chas. Marion) Geller, Lawrence Genest, Raymond (Ray) Genette, Harry James Genovese, Jacob Gensburg Jr., Charles Gentle (alias Charles Riley), 1923-1960 (Box-folder 60/9)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Henry Louis George (alias Hank Louis), John George, Newney George, Roger George, Steve George, Woodrow George, Lawrence Gerald, Ray Gerber, Raymond Gerber, George Gerrard, George W. (William) Gerrick, Ernest Gertson, Arthur C. Gess, Dominick Giarratana, Joe Giaardinello, Neil Fitz-Gibbons, Earl Arthur Gibbs, Ed. Gibson, Harvey (E. or Edd.) Gibson, James E. Gibson, Mike Gibson, Ottis F. Gibson, Robert Gibson (alias Bruce Blaine), Leroy Delbert Giddens, George Everett Giedd, Ronald Dunnells Gifford, Calvin C. Gilbert, Carl Franklin Gilbert, Dean Gilbert, Floyd O. Gilbert, John Douglas Gilbert, M.L. Gilbert, Wilbur Gilbert, Henry Gilbertson, I.A. Giles, Jack L. Giles (alias Leewood Sidney Giles), Bernard Gilham, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 60/10)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Felix Gill, George Gill (alias Iden Green, Golden Green, and Craig Kennedy), Ethel Gillespie, Gene Gillespie, Harold Homer Gillespie, James Francis Gillespie, George Francis Gillespie, Clarence Hubbard Gillette, Donald Edwin Gillette, Harold Gillette, Ray Gilley, William Franklin Gilley, Terrence Gilliland, Daniel D. Gilman, Roy A. Gilman, Vernon Eugene Gilmer, Alfred F. Gilmore, Jack Gilmore, Romeo Gingras, Orville Girard, Andre Giroux, Francis Sylvester Giroux, Walter F. Girton (aka James F. Walker), Roy Gist, Walter Giza, Charles Gladeau, Mike Gladeau, Raymond Gladeau, Tom Gladeau, Raymond Gladue, Willilam Glancy, William J. Glancy, Thomas Glanton (alias Jeff Thompson), Alexander M. Glasoe, Charles William Glasson, Tony Glavinich, Orin R. Gleerup, James P. Gleeson, Hubert James Glenn, Jim Glenn, Leonard K. Glenn, Louis Glenn, Robert Glenn, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 60/11)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Archie Louis Glover, Charles Cecil Glover, Henry Glover, Ben Glusag, Earl Raymond Glynn, David Homer Gneiting, George Goble Jr., James George Godrey, Bruce Godwin, James Hurst Godwin, Walter Godwin, Frank/Franklin Goedert, James Allen Goehring, A.L. Goer, Rufus Goer, Ronald R. Goerlich, Harold Goff, Howard Goforth, John S. Goforth, John T. Goforth, Hayes Gogeles/Goggles, John Morris Gohrick, Rodney Goins, J.A. Goldberg, Herman Golden, Robert Golden, Sidney Eugene Goldsby, Edward V. Golie, Joe Gomeros, Angel Gomez, Arturo Gomez, Felix Gomez, Gilbert Gomez, Jesse Gomez, Joe Gomez, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 60/12)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Albert Gonzales, Laurence Padilla Gonzales, Leandro Gonzales, Luis Gonzales, Manuel Pedro Gonzales Jr., Marvin Gonzales, Pedro Gonzales, Pedro Manuel Gonzales, Ramon/Raymond Gonzales, Ruben Gonzales, Robert W. Good, Lyle Goodchild, Harold D. Goode, Harold R. Goode, Roy Goodhal, Jerry Goodin, Harry Goodland, Raphael Goodman, William R. Goodner (alias Bill King), Wallace Goodrich, James M. Goodwin, James Goodwin (alias J.A. LaVolley), William Goodyer, Jim Gopher, Harold Gordon, Harry L. Gordon, Ira. Gordon, Louis Gordon, Thomas Edward Gordon, Joe Goretti, Thomas P. Gorey, Henry C. Gorham, James Gorman (true name is Harry Drummond), Harry Gosney, Clarence Goss, Jeff David Goss, Silas Goss, Carl Gossett, John Gotham, Phillip Goudry, Ira Gould, Pail Gould, Thomas Gould, Willard Gould, Louis A. Goulet, Jesse Clark Goulette, Gerald Gowdy, Blair Goyins, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 60/13)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Gottlieb Grabatin, Frank Grace, Raymond Grace, James A. Grady, Gloria Graf, Lauren Graff, Lewis A. Graff, Martin Graff, Charles R. Graham, Harold Graham, John Graham, L.J. Graham, Stanley Grams, Ernest Granbois, Robert Granbois, Roy Granby, John Grandovic, Robert Gransbury, Robert L. Grandstaff, Cecil Grant, Claude Grant, Daniel Paul Grant, Eugene Grant, Robert Grant, Douglas John Gravelle, Ray R. Gravelle, Frederick Graves Jr., Joe Graves, John Paul Graves, Leslie Leroy Graves, C.T. Gray, Charles Arthur Gray, Elton Grey, Fred Grey, George Reliance Gray, Herbert Gray, James Gray, Morris Gray, Oliver T. Gray, Raymond Gray, Ronald William Gray, S.C. Gray, Tom Gray, Thomas William Gray, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 60/14)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Maurice Greagan, Charles Green, Charles Green, Donald Green, Donald S. Green, Earl Green, Frank Green, Frederick Carl Green, Gail Borden Green, Gradon Green, Harry Green, Irwin Green, Jack W.L. Green, James Frank Green, John Green, Leard E. Green, Lyal Green, Marion Green, Philip Robert Green, Raymond P. Green (alias Donald R. Nash), Richard Green, Robert Green, Robert A. Green, Wesley L. Green, William Green, Harry Greene, Lawrence John Greene, Raymond P. Greene, Wilbur F. Greene, William Lyonel Greenhalgh, Gerald Greeno, Price Greenup, Roy Greenup, Woody Greenwell, Fred Greer (alias David Lee Adams and Walter Buckmaster), Harold F. Gregg, Walt/Walter Vincent Gregg, Dale Owen Gregory, Guy Gregory, Johnny Mack Gregory, Mark A. Gregory, William M. Gregory (alias Bill Gregory), Larry Robert Greiff, George Greigo, LeRoy Grenier, Steve Gresh, Robert Grey, Stewart Grey, William Charles Grey, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 60/15)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Nicholas J. Gribnau, Herbert Grice, George Griego, Nicolas Ybarbo Griego, Carl Griese, Edward Griffin, Francis Griffin, Freddy Griffin, James Griffin, James W. Griffin, James/Jim Griffin, Louis Griffin, Richard Ross Griffin, Robert H./J. Griffin, William John Griffin, Frank Griffis, Thornton A. Griggs (alias Thornton Alfred Griggs), James R. Grimes, John Grimes, Irene Grimm, Millard Grimmett, John Bovell Grimsley, Floyd Joseph Grina, Jim/James Grinder, Jim Grinder, Jose Grine, Gus Grinsteiner, Joseph Grinstine, B.L. Griswold, Charles Lester Griswold, William Grogan, Thomas Groom, L.E. Grooms, Walter Grooms, Clarence Grosath (alias Jack Grosath), Jacob Groscop, Ben F. Gross, Duane Leroy Gross, Harry Gross Jr., J.P. (Jack) Gross, Pius Gross, John Grossman, Albert J. Grosso, Paul Grosswiler, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 60/16)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Henry Grotbo, Norman Grothe, Edward Grotjan, Jack Grove, Fred I. Grover, George Grovert, Gus Grovert, Walter Donald Groves, Earl Grow, Thurston Grow, Harold Albert Grube, Martin Grundyson, Agustin Guardiola, Christie Paul Guardipee, Coleman Guardipee, Wilson J. Guardipee, Harold Eugene Guenzler, Pedro Guerrero, Fred Guevara, Jack Guider, Jasper Eugene Guinard, Joseph Welmer Guinn, Ralph Guist, Walter Gumm, Earl Gummer, J.M. Gump, Stephen Gundario, John Gunderson, Glenden Gunderson, Robert Gunderson, Frank Gunn, Glenn C. Gunter, Mamie Gurney, William Gushulak, Frank Gusick, Louis Gust, Frank Gustin, Jesus Guterrez, Nick Caldera Guterrez, Lawrence Guthrie, Guermo Gutierez, Joe Gutierz, Arthur William Gutknecht, John Villa Guy, William F. Guy, James Guyeen, Donald Raymond Guyer, Alexander Gwin, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 61/1)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Charley Haabala, Grace Haagenson (alias Grace Angster; Grace Garrity and Betty O'Brien), Arnold Haaland, Howard Raymond Haas, Oscar Haase, Joseph Hackl, Richard Haessly, Charles Haffeman, John Hagan, William Hagan, George Hagberg, Frances Hagen, Roy Hagen, William Hagen, Hollis Horton Haggard, Gerald P. Haggerty, Leo Hagins, Edward H. Hahn, Horace Perry Hailey, John Hails, Jimmy Haines, Harry Hake, Eddie Halcomb, James G. Hale, Mervin Hale, Roy Hale, Wallace Hale, William Hale, William F. Hale, Herbert W. Hales, Robert Haley, Harl Edwin Haley, George E. Halfacre, Art Hall, Clarence Leon Hall, Denver Hall, Ed Hall, Edwin V. Hall, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 61/2)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Ervin Floyd Hall, George Hall, George Hall, Harry Hall, Henry Hall, Jake Hall, Jesse Hall, John Hall, John Allen Hall, Thomas Richard Hall, Viber Hall, W.D. Hall, W.W. Hall, William Hall, Charles Harry Hallam, Cecil Hallford, James Henry Hallock, Gus Halonen, Warren Stuart Halverson, Reidar Halvorsen, David Halvorson, Arthur Hambidge, Alfred Hamel, Raymond Hamel, Edwin Hamilton, Edwin Grant Hamilton, Edwin Grant Hamilton, Herman Hamilton, John A. Hamilton, Leonard Hamilton, Robert Hamilton, Robert Waldo Hamilton, Thomas H. Hamilton, William Albert Hamilton, William H. Hamilton, Woodrow Hamilton, Dale Edward Hamilin, Harold Hamlin, Arthur A. Hamm, Lewis Hammel, Ralph Hammell, Clarence Hammer, Clarence Hammer, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 61/3)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Sam Hammett, Charles Hammick, Charles R. Hammick, C.V. Hammock, Ed Hammond, Ed Hammond, H.O. Hammond, Joe Hammond, Arden Andy Hammons, William Hampel, Harry Hampson, Oscar L. Hampton, Earl E. Hanaford, John Hanberg, George E. Hanchett, Arthur W. Hancock, John Handley, John Handley, Roy Handran, Walter Handy, George Hane, Rex Arlington Haneline, Joe Haney, Lester Haney, William G. Hanika, Lloyd Hankey, Pierre Hanks, Raymond F. Hanks, Walter Hanks, Ed Hanley, Jack Hanley, Guy C. Hanna, Leo C. Hanna, Russ Hannah, Frank Hanneck, Joe Hannon, Chris Hansen, Frederick Hansen, Julius Hansen, Alton Hanson, Carl J. Hanson, Clarence Albert Hanson, Earl B. Hanson, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 61/4)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Gale Hanson, George Albert Hanson, George J. Hanson, H. Marvin Hanson, Hans C. Hanson, Henry H. Hanson, Jack Hanson, Lowell A. Hanson, M.F. Hanson, Magnus Hanson (alias M.F. Hanson), Ole Hanson, Ray Hanson, Willard Hanson, Richard Stanley Happel, Harry B. Happy, Arnold Harala, George Harcharik, Lloyd Harden, Ralph Hardenbrook, James Edward Harder, Carl Hardin, Harold Hardin, D.R. Hardincourt, Frederick W. Harding, Lloyd Harding, Myron R. Hargrave, Rutledge Hargrove, Ed Harkins, James G. Harkins, C.W. Harkness, W.H. Harlow, Alfred Harmon, Edward Harmon, John Harmon, Thomas Harmon, Thomas Harmon, Thomas Henry Harmon, Vern Harmon, Paul E. Harms, Nelo Haro, James Harold, D.C. Harper, Rae L. Harper, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 61/5)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Cloudy Harreil, Carl Oma Harrell, Claude Harrell, H.C. Harrell, Arthur Harrington, Cleo Harrington, Earl Harrington, Ed Harrington, Emmett Harrington, Herbert Harrington, Bob Harris, Charles E. Harris, Charles Leroy Harris, Clark Harris, Donald A. Harris, Donald Hart, Edward Harris, Frank Harris, George Harris, George Harris, Henry Harris, J.R. Harris, Jack D. Harris, Jim Harris, Joe Harris, Joe Harris, Joseph H. Harris, Joseph Harold Harris, Paul A. Harris, Peter Alvin Harris, Richard Harris, William P. Harris, Fred J. Harrison, Lee Harrison, Lynn Harrison, Rex Harrison, Starling Reibel Harrison, Fred Harsha, Arnold Harstad, Kenneth Harstad, Claude Hart, Donald Hart, Glenn L. Hart, Jack D. Hart, Leo Charles Hart, Tex Hart, Fred Harter, Chester Hartford, Vernest Hartford, William Hartford, Ralph Harthouse, Roy Hartlett, Cupid Hartman (alias Stella Harvey), Ronald Lee Hartman, Floyd E. Hartry, John A. Hartry, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 61/6)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Harry Hartsell, Harry Hartung, Michael Harry Hartung, Boyd Hartzell, Bernard L. Harvey, E.H. Harvey, James Harvey, Leo Harvey, William Harvey, Fred Harvill, Joe Harwood, Thomas Haskings (alias Tony Long and James Green), Fay S. Haskins, Thomas Haskins, Orland Benjamin Hassan, Oscar Hasse, Harold M. Hastings, Carl Hatfield, Charles D. Hatfield, Harry E. Hatfield, Donald C. Hathaway, Rex Hathaway, Ray Hatler, George E. Hatten, James Hatton, George H. Hatzenbuehler, Kenneth Haugan, Oscar Haugen, Elton Haughey, Kenneth Haun, Anthony J. Hauptmann, Paul Hauser, Vern Hauserman, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 61/7)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Mike Haver, Howard Clark Haverman, James Hawe, Ben Jay Hawk, Edward Hawk, Missouri Bill Hawk, David Hawkes, Aster H. Hawkins, Delmar Hawkins, Herman E. Hawkins, Jack Hawkins, John Hawkins, William E. Hawkins, Frank Hawley, George Edward Haworth, John W. Hawthorne, Sidney M. Hawver, Donald Robert Hay, George Edwin Hay, John Hay, Clinton Hayes, Floyd E. Hayes, George Hayes, J.B. Hayes, R.J. Hayes, R.J. Hayes, Richard Hayes, Thomas D. Hayes, Marlowe K. Haynes, Arthur M. Hays, G.H. Haye, Marce Hays, William H. Hays, Clarence Benjamin Hayward, Glen Hazelwood, James R. Hazen, William Hazen, Stole Headcarrier, Ernest Healy, Kenneth E. Heard, William Hearsey, William J. Heaston, Reginald Frank Heath, Joe Heather, Myron Louis Heavlin, Richard Heavygun, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 61/8)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Adam Heberlein, William Heckenberg, Mae Hedge, Reuben Hedger, Marx Hedgpeth, Henry C. Hedrick, Edith Heffelfinger, Norman L. Heffelfinger, Charles B. Hefner, Loulie E. Hegdahl, Ray Hegdahl, Jim Heich, Ted Heide, Archie Heim, Albert Heinbaugh, Boyd Heinbaugh, Fred Heinitz, Norman Heise, Edgar F. Heiser, George H. Heiser, Jewell Heiser, John Heisler, Theodore Francis Heisler, Forest Helfer, Gilmore Helgeland, Eugene Arnold Helgeson, James Owen Helm, Louis Helm, Michael Francis Helm, Mellard Helman, Woodrow Charles Helphrey, Richard Helten, Herman J. Helwich, Melvin G. Helwich, Tom Hem, W.L. Hemrick, Huie Hen, A.M. Henerson, Albert Henderson, Frank C. Henderson, Fred A. Henderson, George Henderson, James Henderson, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 61/9)
    - Prisoner description sheets: John Henderson, Thomas Henderson, Wilford Henderson, Eldred D. Hendricks, Eldred D. Hendricks, John Curtis Hendricks, Pete Hendricksmeir, John Hendrickson, Richard L. Hendrickson, Roy Hendrickson, Thomas Hendrickson, Marvin Hendrix, Joseph L. Hendry, Donald Heninger, Raymond H. Henley, Thomas Joe Henly, Churchill Henry, George Ray Henry, Joseph Edward Henry, Less Henry, Lester B. Henry, Carl Hensley, George Harold Herbenson, Orville Herman, Thomas Edward Herman, Walter Herman, William C. Hermann, Pete Hermansen, Joe Hernandes, Augustine Hernandez, Hilario Hernandez, Lorenso Hernandez, Tony Hernandez, Antonio Herrera, Emigeleo Herrera, Luis Herrera, Carroll E. Herrick, Charles Herrick, Allyn Dean Herried, Leslie Herrin, Alan H. Herring, Joseph Herring Jr., Jack P. Herron, Clifford P. Hersey, William Hersha, Junior Pete Herzet, Michael Herzog, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 61/10)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Ed Hess, Frank Hess, Ernest R. Hesse, Arthur Thomas Heaterly, Chester K. Hewitt, Emery Hewitt, John Hewitt, Marvin Heyd, B.C. Heykes, R.O. Hickey, Joe Hicks, John Hicks, Walter Hicks, Vernon Hickson, John Hiebert, Steve Higgins, William A. High, Isaac Highland, Willie Hightower, Perfecto Higuera, Jesse Hildebran, Edgar J. Hildenbrand, Charles Hildermann, Francis Hilger, Charles Hill, Clayton Hill, Daniel Hill, Dixon Hill, Douglas Jerome Hill, Edward Russell Hill, Emmett J. Hill, George Hill, Gordon Hill, Guy Hill, Howard T. Hill, J.W. Hill, Joe Hill, John Hill, John Hill (alias Jack Burt and Fritz Hileman), John Wesley Hill, Lawrence Hill, Melbourne M. Hill, Raymond Hill, Robert Hill, Rudolph Robert Hill, Thomas Franklin Hill, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 61/11)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Leo Martin Hillicker, Horace Glen Hills, Romoe Romalice Hills, John W. Hilton, Chung Hin, Elmer Hinchey, Albert Hinchman, Alfred Tomkins Hindley, Joe D. Hindman, Robert John Hines, Charley Hing, Mah Sam Hing, Tom Hing, Archie Hinkie, David William Hinkle, Frank Hinkle, James Hinkle, Pete Hinkles, Henry Hinkley, Edgar George Hinman, Walter Hinze, James E. Hirst, William Hissong, Russell Hitson, Leo Hittle, Charles Hixon, Guy LeRoy Hixon, John L. Hoban, Simon F. Hobbs, Wallace Hobbs, William Alvin Hobart, John Hoban, G.O. Hoberg, Norman Ray Hochstrasser, James H. Hockspier, Russell Hodge, Fred Hodgson, Robert K. Hodgson, Homer Hodke, Richard M. Hodke, William H. Hoehl, Dave Hoff, Louis Hoff, Jacob William Hofferber, Alex Hoffert, Clayton Hoffine, Bill Hoffman, Charles A. Hoffman, Glen Hoffman, Joseph Hoffman, Leo Hoffman, Louis Hoffman, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 61/12)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Martiin Hofland, Frank Hogan, Joe Hogan, John Hogan, Mickey Hogan, Pete Hogan, William F. Hogan, James Hogge, DeForrest Hogue, William Hogue, Kenneth Hohrman, Einard Hoikkala, Donald Holasch, Belmont Holbrook, Wallace Holbrook, Walter Wardsey Holcomb (alias Walter Spahtt), Forney Lee Halcombe, Charles E. Holden, Everett Norman Holden, E.L. Holder, Fred Holen, Arthur Holien, Arthur Holland, Dan Holland, Jewel Holland, H.T. Holland, Pat Holland, Ray Holland, Robert Holland, E.J. Hollas, Fred Hollers, Russell Hollester, Pat Hollingsworth, Alvie Hollis Jr., Devereaux A. Hollowell, Lloyd Robert Hollum, Jack Holly, Edward Ernest Holmberg, Al J. Holman, Cleo Holmes, Herbert F. Holmes, John S. Holmes, Monte Holmes, Robert Holmes, Woodrow Holmes, James L. Holmgren, Robert G. Holmin, Monte Holms, Walter Holst, Ira Holt, Jack Holt (alias Curly Williams; Harry Williams and Harry Beauchamp), John Holton Jr., George Holvorsen, Adam Holzer, Ruben Holzworth, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 61/13)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Lee M. Honderich, Robert Hood, Sam Hood, Homer E. Hoon, Martin Hoops, Frederick Hoornaert, Bernard Hoover, George James Hoover, Harold Hoover, Harry Hoover, Lloyd Clinton Hoover, Abel Hopkins Jr., Clyde L. Hopkins, Domnic Hopkins, James Hopkins, Robert F. Hopkins, Willie Hopkins, August Hoppe, Louis R. Hoppe, Billy Gene Hooper, Charles Ray Hopper, Howard R. Hopper, William J. Horan, Albert Horn, Harold Horn, Joe Horn, Robert Horn, Rufus Horn, Victor Horn, George Hornbeck, Clarence Horner, Clifford Horner, Hallie Horner, Warren Horner, Alvin Adam Horning, Ben F. Horton, Homer Hoskins, Sidney Hoskins, Albert E. Hoth, Clyde Hotchkiss, Gloyd Elwin Hotchkiss, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 61/14)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Wallace D. Houde, Floyd Houdeshell, Royal Houger, Austin N. Hough, Robert Earl Houghton, Henry Houle, William R. Houlihan, Carl Houliston, Adolf Houn, Harvey J. House, Joe Houser, Everett Housman, Dominic R. Houston, Gene Houston (alias Gene Northern), John Houts, Bennie Hovde, Dick Howard, Edward L. Howard, Eugene H. Howard, Golden Guy Howard, Harry E. Howard, Henry C. Howard, Hugh Howard, Jack Howard, John C. Howard, Joseph Howard, Leonard E. Howard, Ray Howard, Eugene James Howe, Howard D. Howe, Laurel Howe, R.C. Howe, Myrl Howell, Ray L. Howell (alias Ray Sparks), Ross Howell, Sam Howell, Charles Howland, Edward Hoyt, Ernest S. Hoyt, Walter Hoyt, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 62/1)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Frank Hrouda, Mike Hrubis, Dick Hubbard, Harold Melton Hubbard, Michael G. Huber, Thomas J. Huber, E.F. Hubert, James O. Hubert (alias Tom Wylie), Ralph William Huckabay, Jack Hude, Cornelius Hudler, Glen R. Hudnall, Claud Hudson, Ernest C. Hudson, Joe Hudson, Leslie Hudson, Lewis H. Hudson, Norman C. Hudson, Raymond Herman Hudson, Jesse Lee Huff, Lawrence Huff, Adam Huffman, George Huffman, Harry H. Huffman, Jesse M. Huffman, Lloyd Huffman, Arthur Hughes, Fred Hughes, Fred Hughes, Frederick Robert Michael Hughes, Greeley Hughes, J.P. Hughes, James M. Hughes, Robert Hughes, Warren S. Hughes, Dannie Sue Hughett, Theodore Huhn, Enoch Hukoveh, Arthur E. Hulker, Gene Hull, Gerald Joseph John Hull, Howard Hull, Howard Thomas Hulse, James Hulsey, Louis Frank Hulvey, Frank Human, F.J. Humbert Jr., Joseph P. Humbrecht, Joseph P. Humbrecht, Larry William Hume, James Monroe Humphres, James Humphrey, Ray Humplett, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 62/2)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Arnold H. Hunt (alias H.G. Grimes), Ed Hunt, Harold Hunt, Harold Hunt, Henry Hunt, Irvan Albert Hunt, J.C. Hunt, Perry Hunt, Richard A. Hunt, Richard A. Hunt, E.B. Hunter, Lawrence Hunter, William L. Hunter, James C. Huntington, Eldon Harold Huntsman, Walter Hurd (alias Robert Moates), Dayton Hurin, Joe Hurlbert, Richard Hurlburt (alias Tom E. Dooley), Alvin S. Hurley, Skiles Hurley, John Leo Hurnick, Russell Hurst, Eugene F. Hurt, Rose Husted, James Hutchens (alias John Ray Kidd), Elmer Hutchins, James Hutchins, Russell Hutchins, Richard Hutchinson, Roy Hutchinson, Kenneth Hutchison, Andrew Hyatt, Eugene Hyatt, George Hyatt, John Edward Hydes, Kenneth Theodore Hymer, Clifford I. Hyre, Robert A. Hysell, William Hysmith, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 62/3)